(Sheldon:)All right.
Let's just finish cooking.
Well... Hey. O-Okay.
Let me make this up to you.
(Leonard:)Sometimes I keep
an online journal.
(Leonard:)I want you to read
something that I write.
(Penny:)Okay, really, I'm fine.
Okay.
(Leonard:)Well, then I'll read it to you.
(Leonard:)It's from the day we first met.
(clears throat)
"Beauty, thy name is Penny."
Oh, God.
(Penny:)Stop.
(Penny:)I don't want you
(Leonard:)to read something
you think'll just butter me up.
(Penny:)I want to hear
the most recent thing you wrote.
(Amy:)Fine.
(Leonard:)Mmm...
"Penny's beauty,
like our love,
(Leonard:)grows more with
each passing day."
(Penny:)Does it really say that?
(high-pitched):
Why would I lie?
"OMG. OMG.
"We're so close
to the new Star Wars.
"I can't take it.
Gah."
"Gah"?
(Leonard:)Well, you didn't
read it right.
The new Star Wars
is coming. Gah!